robofx.com 2017-06-20

# PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY
               ROBOFOREX (CY) LTD
               Soboh House 377, 28th October Street
               Office #1, 3107, Limassol, Cyprus

       ROBOFOREX (CY) LTD
       Soboh House 377, 28th October Street
       Office #1, 3107, Limassol, Cyprus
                                                          PRIVACY POLICY
Client’s Privacy is important, that is why RoboForex (CY) Ltd protects the information Client shares with the
Company. RoboForex (CY) Ltd uses the shared information only for investment services it is eligible to provide
according to its License 191/13, grunted by EU regulator - CySEC.
To protect Client’s Privacy RoboForex (CY) Ltd follows different principles in accordance with worldwide practices for
Customer Privacy and Data Protection:
    1. RoboForex (CY) Ltd doesn’t sell or give away the Client’s name, mail address, phone number, email address,
         or any other information to anyone who is not involved into the business/investment services.
    2. RoboForex (CY) Ltd uses state-of-the-art security measures to protect Client’s information from
         unauthorized users.
NOTICE
RoboForex (CY) Ltd will ask the Client when it needs information that personally identifies the Client (Personal
Information) and/or allows RoboForex (CY) Ltd to contact the Client. Generally, this information is requested when
the Client creates a Registration ID on the site or when he downloads free software. RoboForex (CY) Ltd uses
Personal Information for four primary purposes:
    1.   To make the site easier to use by not having to enter information more than once.
    2.   To help quickly find software, services or information.
    3.   To create the content most relevant to a specific Client.
    4.   To alert the Client about product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from
         RoboForex (CY) Ltd.
CONSENT
After the registration the Client is able to select the kinds of information he wants to receive from the Company by
subscribing to various services, like electronic newsletters. If the Client doesn’t want to be communicated with,
regarding the Company’s products, offers, programs, events, or services by email, postal mail, or by telephone, he
can select the option stating that he doesn’t wish to receive marketing messages from the Company and/or from
third parties.
ACCESS
RoboForex (CY) Ltd provides the Client with the means to ensure that his Personal Information is correct and up-to-
date. Client can review and update this information at any time at the “Members area”, where he may:
    1. View, edit and update personal information he has shared.
    2. Underline whether he wants Company (or third party) to send him marketing information by postal mail.
    3. Sign up for electronic newsletters about Company’s products and services.
SECURITY
RoboForex (CY) Ltd has taken strong measures to protect the security of Personal Information. Company takes strong
precautions to protect Client’s data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction.
                   TEL: +357-25-123275 FAX: +357-25-580077        EMAIL: info@roboforex.eu   WEB: www.roboforex.eu
                               AUTHORIZED AND REGULATED BY THE CYPRUS SECURITIES AND EXCHANGE COMISSION
                                           LICENSE №: 191/13 | REGISTRATION NUMBER: HE310464

        ROBOFOREX (CY) LTD
        Soboh House 377, 28th October Street
        Office #1, 3107, Limassol, Cyprus
RoboForex (CY) Ltd guarantees Client’s e-transaction to be 100% safe and secure. When Client places the order or
access the Personal Account Information, he is utilizing secure server software SSL, which encrypts Personal
Information before it’s sent over the Internet. SSL is one of the safest encryption technologies available.
Client’s Personal Information is never shared outside the Company without his preliminary permission and according
to STANDARD TERMS OF BUSINESS FOR CLIENTS RoboForex (CY) Ltd. Inside the Company all Client’s data is stored in
password-controlled systems with limited access. Client’s information may be stored and processed in Cyprus or any
other country where RoboForex (CY) Ltd, its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents are located.
In accordance with the current legislation, recording, systematization, collection, storing, update, and acquisition of
the personal information of the Russian Federation citizens must be performed in the databases located within the
Russian Federation.
The Client himself has a significant role in protecting his Personal Information. No one can see or edit his Personal
Information without knowing his user name and password.
ENFORCEMENT
If for some reason Client believes RoboForex (CY) Ltd has not adhered to these principles, Client can notify the
Company by email info@roboforex.eu and Company will do its best to determine and correct the problem promptly.
RoboForex (CY) Ltd will disclosure the Client’s Personal Information, without notice, only if required to do so by law
or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:
     1. Confirm to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on RoboForex (CY) Ltd.
     2. Protect and defend the rights or property of RoboForex (CY) Ltd.
                    TEL: +357-25-123275 FAX: +357-25-580077        EMAIL: info@roboforex.eu   WEB: www.roboforex.eu
                                AUTHORIZED AND REGULATED BY THE CYPRUS SECURITIES AND EXCHANGE COMISSION
                                            LICENSE №: 191/13 | REGISTRATION NUMBER: HE310464
